Alright, in this clip we'll be doing the upper body on our cute, more cartoonized angel, and we're just going to give him a simple, white robe.
So we're going to start by drawing his neck in there like that, maybe give him sort of a v-neck shape to his robe there.
Draw the top edges of it.
Now, we're just going to come down and do his shoulders, just like that.
Swing down, swoop down and give him some flowing robes here.
We're going to draw the sleeves coming into his side like that, and as you draw his robe coming down to where his belt would be, kind of give it a little bit of a outward curve, so that when you come in and draw his belt, like that, it leaves a little bit of a realistic little space where the fabric would kind of bend in there like that, like that.
You add a little swooping detail to the robe like that, and then just draw his hands in there.
Standard cartoon hands, with the four fingers.
This guy definitely looks like he's wishing us peace on earth and good will to men.
And there.
You got the top of his robe, his sleeves, little belt there, his hands, and that will work well for his upper body.
And in the next clip we'll move on to the lower half of his body.